### JEHOSHABEATH AKOSUA AFRAKOMA APPIAH

SSHABEATH@GMAIL.COM Telephone: +233(0)503423686

Accra.

#### **PROFILE**

A current Software Development student at OpenLabs Ghana (NIIT) and a graduate of the Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology with a degree in Political Studies and French, with a one- year work experience in administrative assistance at the National Service Scheme, Headquarters. I am a highly motivated and goal- oriented individual committed to carrying out my duties professionally and efficiently. I am proactive, reliable and able to perform duties with little to no supervision.

### **EDUCATION**

OpenLabs Ghana (NIIT) SEPTEMBER 2021 till present

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology *AUGUST 2020* - BA POLITICAL STUDIES

Wesley Girls' High School MAY 2015 – GENERAL ARTS

### **EXPERIENCE**

NATIONAL SERVICE SCHEME (HEAD OFFICE)

Administrative assistant September 2020 – August 2021

# Key Responsibilities:

- Contributed to the smooth running of the office of the Executive Director by providing front desk administrative work.
- Receiving visitors, solely for the office of the Executive Director, thus contributing to the decongestion of the main reception.
- Making, receiving and forwarding calls as per the operations of the office.
- Taking messages and providing assistance to visitors and callers.
- Ensuring continuity of service provision by sitting in for the personal secretaries of the director and carrying out some of their duties.

# MULTIMEDIA GROUP LIMITED (KUMASI)

Receptionist May 2018 - July 2018

## Key Responsibilities:

- Contributed to the continued interactions between the company and its clients by receiving and directing visitors.
- Increasing productivity by making, receiving and forwarding calls to all offices.
- Taking messages from callers and visitors.
- Occasionally typing announcements, news articles and memos to ease the hassle in the appropriate offices.

# **SKILLS**

'HTML 'CSS 'JavaScript 'REACT

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

• Bachelor of Arts in Political Studies and French.

- Certificate of Completion in Programming Foundations: Fundamentals (Linkedin Learning)
- Certificate of Completion in Interpersonal Communication (Project Management Institute, Inc)
- Certificate of Completion in Dealing with Difficult People in Your Office (Linkedin Learning)